Georgios Antzigai

Phone +447874087867

E-mail <u>george.adzhygai@gmail.com</u>

Citizenship EU, Greece Residence London, UK

LinkedIn https://www.linkedin.com/in/ayorgo

GitHub https://github.com/ayorgo

StackOverflow https://stackoverflow.com/users/4755520/ayorgo

The latest version of this CV https://github.com/ayorgo/cv/blob/master/georgios-antzigai-cv.pdf

Summary

Full stack machine learning engineer able to deliver solutions starting from data collection to establishing continuous integration pipelines.

I have experience in inferential statistics, supervised machine-learning and exploratory data analysis with applications mostly in **Python** using various dialects of **SQL**. I also build machine learning pipelines both locally and on AWS.

Experience

Machine Learning Engineer

Nov 2019 - now

LYST <u>lyst.com</u>

I build and maintain machine learning pipelines on AWS using python, SQL and bash. I also take part in building information retrieval and recommendation models.

Lead Data Scientist

May 2018 - Nov 2018

ETX Capital etxcapital.com

Applying python to machine learning, data analysis, and reporting.

- Established the python development and deployment pipelines for the company
- Built a classification model using scikit-learn + statsmodels packages for the model itself and pandas + matplotlib
 + seaborn for exploratory data analysis and data cleansing
- Productionised the above model in a form of RESTful APIs using Flask and Microsoft IIS
- Delivered numerous reporting solutions of various complexity using python and T-SQL
- Led a team of two data scientists

Self studying Data Science

Apr 2017 – May 2018

I quit my software development job to pursue my passion and dedicate all of my time and resources to studying probability, statistics, data analysis and machine learning

Software Engineer

Jun 2015 - Mar 2017 (1 year 10 months)

Zopa zopa.com

Worked on company's peer-to-peer lending platform:

- As a software engineer designed and enhanced core parts of the platform such as matching engine and repayment processing using C#
- As an occasional data analyst built advanced reporting solutions in T-SQL

Experienced Engineer

Jun 2014 - Feb 2015 (9 months)

InsightSoftware.com insightsoftware.com

Contributed to both server and client ends of company's bespoke BI system:

- Fixed and enhanced system's core SQL generating engine written in C#
- Maintained local JavaScript-based SVG graphics library including thorough refactoring, performance enhancements and development of key new features

.NET Developer

Apr 2013 – May 2014 (1 year 2 months)

EPAM Systems, Barclay's development center epam.com

Maintained, redesigned and enhanced corporate banking software within various teams or acting independently:

- Developed a set of multi-tier WCF services
- · Created a data import and processing tool using advanced SQL and existing scheduling engine
- Set up continuous integration pipelines for the above-mentioned projects using TeamCity along with unit testing, code quality control (StyleCop and Sonar), and NuGet package management

.NET Web Developer

Sep 2011 - Apr 2013 (1 year 7 months)

Terrasoft <u>bpmonline.com</u>

Developed a web-based CRM on both front and back ends:

- · Created a number of UI web controls using ExtJS, CSS, and HTML
- Integrated the Highcharts interactive library
- Developed various back-end solutions using C#, WCF, ASP.NET, and T-SQL

Senior System Dev. Consultant

Feb 2006 - Apr 2011 (5 years)

SimCorp Ukraine LLC simcorp.com

Developed and maintained custom investment management system within a team of 3 developers:

- · Built data extraction/analysis utility using Dyalog APL and PL/SQL
- Took part in various development projects across the company as a senior consultant

Education

National Technical University of Ukraine "Kyiv Polytechnic Institute"

2005 - 2007

Solid-state physics, PhD study (not complete)

Approximate analytical model of anisotropic coordinate-sensitive radiation detector, comparison to numerical 3D-simulation. With the numerical simulation, a system of second-order nonlinear differential equations was solved taking into account the heats released (absorbed) by eddy thermoelectric currents:

- Snarskii A. A. Adzhigai G. V. Ascheulov A. A. Coordinate-sensitive anisotropic radiation detector. Analytical description and numerical simulation. Journal of Thermoelectricity. 2005, No. 1. - p.80-86.
- Snarskii A. A. Adzhigai G. V. Bezsudnov I. V. On the inherent figure of merit of thermoelectric composites. Journal
 of Thermoelectricity. 2005, No.4. p.74-81. http://arxiv.org/abs/cond-mat/0609447

National Technical University of Ukraine "Kyiv Polytechnic Institute"

1999 - 2005

Applied mathematics, MSc

Courses

Machine Learning by Stanford University

Jan 2017

Coursera https://www.coursera.org/account/accomplishments/verify/K6DZA8FSAPKP